A Guide to the Papers of Creed Taylor
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Receipt: Creed Taylor, Jr., 1858 (Box Box 3)
- Bill: William M. Carroll to Creed Taylor, 1858-59 (Box Box 3)
- Emily Taylor to Mrs. Lucy Taylor, 1859 January 27 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: Creed Taylor, Jr., 1858 March 2 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: B. Gould to Creed Taylor, 1859 April 5 (Box Box 3)
- Albert Taylor Bledsoe to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1859 September 1 (Box Box 3)
- Albert Howard, Jr. to Jennette Knickerbocker, 1859 September 13 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: Southern Protection Insurance Co. to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1859 October 18 (Box Box 3)
- Account: Creed Taylor, Jr. with Thomas M. Noble, 1859 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: D. Brown to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1860 January 14 (Box Box 3)
- William F. Taylor to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1860 April 13 (Box Box 3)
- John Manning to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1860 June 13 (Box Box 3)
- Tax Receipt: G.M. Ryals to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1860 (Box Box 3)
- Emily Taylor to Mrs. Creed Taylor, Jr., [ca. 1860] (Box Box 3)
- Jennette Knickerbocker on "The Importance of Right Principles", [ca. 1860] (Box Box 3)
- Albert Howard, Jr. on "The Triumphs of Labor and the Money Power", [ca. 1860] (Box Box 3)
- W.F. Taylor to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1861 August 2 (Box Box 3)
- Richard P. Walton to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1863 August 26 (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor, Jr. to David Griffith, Re: salt rationing, 1863 August 31 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt, 1863 November (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: M.I. Glasson to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1864 January 19 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: Creed Taylor, Jr., 1864 March 3 (Box Box 3)
- I.O.U.: William W. Evans to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1864 September 1 (Box Box 3)
- Deed: Creed Taylor, Jr. and Lucy M. Taylor to James [ ], 1864 September 28 (Box Box 3)
- Receipt: Creed Taylor, Jr., 1864 October 15 (Box Box 3)
- Check: J. D. Christian, 1865 January 22 (Box Box 3)
- Military pass: J. L. Baker for Mr. Taylor and servant, 1865 April 19 (Box Box 3)
- Jennette Howard to Albert Howard, 1866 February 21 (Box Box 3)
- William G. Taylor to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1866 November 13 (Box Box 3)
- Power of Attorney: W. Taylor, Executor of Samuel Taylor, Appomattox Co., 1866 November 13 (Box Box 3)
- S.C. Gholson to Creed Taylor, Jr., 1866 November 29 (Box Box 3)
- S.C. Gholson to Mrs. Lucy Taylor, 1873 March 28 (Box Box 3)
- Appeal bond from decree of county court (Box Box 3)
- N. Dodson to Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Form for bond (Box Box 3)
- "The Future of the Republic", n.d. (Box Box 3)
- George Hay to Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to Mrs. Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to Mrs. Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to Mrs. Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to Mrs. Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to Mrs. Sally Taylor (Box Box 3)
- J.R. To Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- J. M. Randolph to Creed Taylor, fragment (Box Box 3)
- Memo: Mr. Pendleton's memo on tenure of the registrar of the land office (Box Box 3)
- Benjamin Watkins Leigh to Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Judges Wilson & Leigh, broadside, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Lucy B. Randolph to Mrs. Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Martha Randolph to Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Spencer Roane to Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Spencer Roane to Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Andrew Stevenson to Creed Taylor (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor to John Wickham, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor to William S. Ryland (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor: List of order books in Richmond superior court of chancery (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor on Mr. Hay in the case of Nicolson & Heth vs. Hancock et.al., fragment, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Commonwealth vs. William W. Hening, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Letter, correspondents unkown (Box Box 3)
- Creed Taylor: Opinion in the case of Samuel Dew and E. Stribling, endorsement by Spencer Roane (Box Box 3)
- Virginia vs. John Wheeler, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- [ ] to Creed Taylor, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Ann Cary Randolph to Mrs. Creed Taylor "Needham", 11 letters, 1 copy, 1 fragment (Box Box 3)